This video introduces the new update of Closet.
We have introduced a new function, the sticker editor, to improve your design ability.
As in Closet, users can now edit stickers on 3D clothing in Closet.
First, enter the content page.
On the right side, click the button to enter the new tool.
In the 3D tool bar, select the edit sticker tool.
Then click the sticker.
The sticker will show the shape controller around it.
We can use the shape controller to adjust the sticker.
First, drag the triangle around the controller.
You can adjust the width and length according to the proportion of the picture.
Another way is like this.
You can Veterans your village or habr Cloud.
Drag the outer circle around the controller to rotate the picture.
Press the center key, and shift the key fo the controller.
You can now adjust the position.
Under the material option on the right, select the basic parameters.
Click to replace the icon.
Select the sticker from the folder.
Click to open.
Now the sticker has been replaced with a new icon.
You can also adjust its position, proportion, angle, etc.
You can also adjust its position, proportion, etc.
Through the sticker configuration tool,
even those who do not have CLO software can also participate in the design and development.
Now let's introduce another new function, content analysis.
Through this function,
you can actually check the progress and content activity analysis of the work process.
First,
go to the content page.
Click on the content analysis button in the upper right corner,
then you can enter the content analysis page.
The work process analysis provides the progress of the work process
and the draft of the development cycle.
The total delivery cycle in the upper right corner shows the number of days passed since the content was created.
The time axis in the middle shows the delivery cycle between each work flow state.
This is where the time axis for all work flows.
When the mouse is suspended in a specific work flow,
it shows the number of activities in each status.
You can see the upload, broadcast, communication, and download of its versions.
Below the time axis,
the activity analysis provides a detailed activity date.
In the upper right corner, you can switch to the display of bubble chart or pile chart.
You can adjust the display area size by rolling.
Through the activity analysis table, you can identify the fundamental reasons for extending the delivery period.
We can quickly find out which activities are the most active and support our strategic decisions.